berettausa.com 2008-12-17

# Beretta USA

**Privacy Policy**  
  
To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Beretta site.

The security of your personal information is very important to us. The personal information that you provide to us on our website when you register or update an account, enter a contest or promotion, shop online or place an order telephonically (i.e. name, address, telephone number and e-mail address) is maintained in private files on our secure Web servers and our internal systems. Beretta shares information about our customers with some of our affiliated companies and reputable third parties in order to help us provide better service to you. These third parties may be given access to some or all of the information you provide to us. Beretta requires these third parties to maintain your information in the strictest confidence. Also we will not sell, rent or share your email address with others for them to send you unsolicited email. 

**What Personal Information We Collect**

**  
IP Address**

When you browse berettausa.com you do so anonymously. Personal information, including your e-mail address, is not collected. Your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) is logged on our server to give us an idea of which parts of our web site you are visiting and how long you are spending there. We do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable. 

**  
If You Are Shopping in the Beretta e-Store **

**Cookies**

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart if you are in the e-Store, to monitor on line surveys that you may have taken and to assist you in navigation on our website. When shopping in the Beretta e-Store, your cookie is like taking a number for a service when entering a store. Your selections are stored on our server, not your computer. This is like asking a clerk to hold your merchandise while you continue to shop. When you are done shopping, and ready to check out, your cookie identifies which selections of merchandise belong to you. This cookie contains no personal information about you and no one but Beretta can retrieve your cookie. Cookies are not required to browse our site but they are required to place an order. 

If you prefer not to turn on cookies to browse this site, and you would like to purchase merchandise, you can and call us at 1-800-636-3420 to place your order. We are open Monday – Friday through 9:00-5:00 Eastern Standard Time. At other hours, you may leave your order on our secure Beretta Interactive Customer Support Agent (BICS) telephone answering system. You may also fax your order to 301-283-0189, or mail your order to: Beretta Customer Support, 17601 Beretta Drive, Accokeek, MD 20607. When placing your order, please have your payment information ready or enclose it with your order.

**Our On-Line e-Store Order Form**

We collect visitor's contact information (like their e-mail address) and financial information (like their credit card numbers) as part of the ordering process. When you make a purchase using a credit card, we collect your name, your billing address for the card, the card type, number, and expiration date. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase, to ship your order, to send you an e-mail confirmation or to resolve a question about your transaction. If you are having your order shipped to an address other than your billing address, we also collect the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s). We do not store credit card numbers or expiration dates on this web site and do not aggregate credit card information with any other information we may collect on the site.

**  
How We Protect the Security of Your Personal Information**

The security of your personal information is very important to us. 

In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet. 

Beretta has also obtained a digital certificate from Thawte, a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secure portion of our site (which is any page containing any of your personal information), an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser window. If you click on this image, a small popup window displaying site-security information will appear. This certificate guarantees that your personal information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form to a Beretta server, not to some unknown or unauthorized server. 

Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you created an account at the Beretta e-Store (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No customer support representative or any other representative of Beretta will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect.

**Contact Information**

Our site's warranty registration, gun lock, email newsletters, catalog and manual request forms, and order forms require users to give us contact information (such as their name, address and e-mail address). The customer's contact information is used to process requests, validate product warranty registrations and permits us to contact the visitor if necessary. In some instances, we also collect information about your preferences. We use your preference information to better serve you when sending out announcements on Beretta events, promotions and product announcements. When we send you e-mails, we also provide you with the necessary information about how to opt out from receiving future e-mails. 

**How to Opt Out**

If you wish to opt out from e-mails from Beretta, send an e-mail to berettausa@cs.net with the subject line of "Remove." We will exclude you from future e-mails.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

This site contains links to other sites. Please note that berettausa.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Disclaimer**

This policy may be changed at any time without notice at Beratta’s discretion. 

Policy Updated on 30 Nov 05
